<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-01-29T15:53:23-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Matt’s Killer Webpage Dude</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">woottitle</title><link href="/2025/01/29/woot.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="woottitle" /><published>2025-01-29T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-29T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2025/01/29/woot</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/29/woot.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="hah">HAH</h1>
<p>#fuckers</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blogpost" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[HAH #fuckers]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">This is a title!</title><link href="/2025/01/26/FirstPost.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="This is a title!" /><published>2025-01-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2025/01/26/FirstPost</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/26/FirstPost.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="yeah">Yeah</h1>

<p>THis is my first post</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/Pasted image 20250127233702.png" alt="blah" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blogpost" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Purpose and Meaning</title><link href="/asshat/2025/01/26/PurposePost.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Purpose and Meaning" /><published>2025-01-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/asshat/2025/01/26/PurposePost</id><content type="html" xml:base="/asshat/2025/01/26/PurposePost.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="header-of-the-page">Header of the page</h1>
<p>Welcome to my page assholes.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Hah did you see that</p>
</blockquote>

<div class="language-bash highlighter-rouge"><div class="highlight"><pre class="highlight"><code>ps <span class="nt">-lah</span>
<span class="nb">exit</span>
</code></pre></div></div>

<ul>
  <li>List of things</li>
  <li>1</li>
  <li>2</li>
  <li>3</li>
</ul>

<p>1) stuff
2) and
3) things
4) yeah</p>

<h2 id="the-book-in-3-sentences">🚀The Book in 3 Sentences</h2>
<ul>
  <li>This is a book on how to be a man, spiritually, which is to give your gift (through your purpose) and make love to your woman and world and dissolve by freedom into bliss. Passion in relationships are a product of the polarization between masculine and feminine and ways to keep the passion alive are discussed. Push on your edges and follow your lust for world / woman.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="-impressions">🎨 Impressions</h3>
<ul>
  <li>The author certainly bring a lot of spirituality that I am familiar with (nondualism) and his take on sexuality/spirituality resonates with mine. I want to read more of his works on sex and spirituality.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="who-should-read-it">📖Who Should Read It?</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Men who want to understand the deep meaning and fulfillment in being a man.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="️-how-the-book-changed-me">☘️ How the Book Changed Me</h3>
<ul>
  <li>I should not be afraid of lust/attraction. Own your desires.</li>
  <li>I know now that polarization is critical for passionate relationships. Always remain in your masculine.</li>
  <li>Purpose is the most important thing to a man.</li>
  <li>Don’t get lost in work/tasks.</li>
  <li>Take sexual yoga seriously.</li>
  <li>Remain relaxed and breathe correctly.</li>
  <li>Reinforced that “I am already full”. I need nothing but to give my gift. I am born a sacrifice.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="️-my-top-10-quotes">✍️ My Top 10 Quotes</h3>
<ul>
  <li>“To be free is to die to your need to be a separate self. What, then, could be constrained? Ego death, absolute surrender to the point of oneness, is the ultimate freedom. Few men ever release themselves enough to relax in this depth of freedom because they are afraid of absolutely no stress. No stress means no thoughts, no sense of protected self, no mission to accomplish. The end of the masculine game. Yet, this stress-free, unprotected end of the game is exactly what you are always seeking, through orgasm, financial killings, or winning a war. You are willing to experience lesser forms of masculine “death” and ecstasy, but you are unwilling to face the death of your separate self-sense, and finally be the freedom you have only allowed yourself to taste in moments.”</li>
  <li>“A person who denies their own essence and hides their true desires is divided and unable to relax into the full openness of love.”</li>
  <li>Your fear is the sharpest definition of your self. You should know it. You should feel it virtually constantly. Fear needs to become your friend, so that you are no longer uncomfortable with it. — location: <a href="kindle://book?action=open&amp;asin=B01NA993PI&amp;location=500">500</a> ^ref-11446</li>
  <li>“If you are disconnected to your deep masculine core of purpose and consciousness, you will also be disconnected from a woman’s depth. You will only be attracted to the superficial display of a woman’s radiance”</li>
  <li>“The play of your body wanting her body is the most obvious hoax of fulfillment.”</li>
  <li>“Your ultimate desire is for the union of consciousness with its own luminosity, wherein all appearance is recognized as your deep, blissful nature, and there is only One. Your desire for union with a woman is a stepped-down version of this ultimate spiritual need. You can use your desire as a doorway to spiritual oneness. Magnify your desiring to the brink of madness. Sustain it with full breath, relaxed body, and open heart. Embrace your woman, if you have one, and give her what you want from her. Give it all to her. Give it away to her. Give her so much of what you want from her that you can’t tell who is who, the chaser has become the tail, and all motion stops in the intensity of self-release. There is only One. The very light of your consciousness shines as the world, and it is looking back at you, appearing as woman. She often appears as what you most fear and desire. She is the goddess, ready to fuck you, murder you, and enlighten you. Her appearance and your desire can be an endless drama of need, or they can merge, becoming a doorway to your divine source.”</li>
</ul>

<h1 id="main-points">Main Points</h1>

<h3 id="you-are-awareness-and-you-must-engage-in-the-world-from-this-place">You are awareness, and you must engage in the world from this place</h3>
<p>Everything is superficial and empty if it isn’t floating in the deep sea of your conscious awareness and loving. You are to endlessly ravish your woman and the world.</p>

<h3 id="a-superior-man">A Superior Man..</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Strives to be Shiva (the divine masculine, all-pervading, fully present, cannot be bent to his woman’s wiles)</li>
  <li>Lives from the realization of the core of being (source)</li>
  <li>is purposeful</li>
  <li>is confident</li>
  <li>is directed</li>
  <li>is integrity</li>
  <li>is humorous</li>
  <li>is sensitive</li>
  <li>is spontaneous</li>
  <li>is spiritually alive</li>
  <li>Can love from a place of pain</li>
  <li>Is pushing his edges. He lives at the edges of discomfort and does not settle for mediocrity</li>
  <li>Does not betray his knowledge/intuition to please a woman</li>
  <li>Fucks both his woman and his world to smithereens. No gifts left ungiven. Lose and gain everything. No limit to depth of being. Die blissfully though a crucifixion of pain and pleasure.</li>
  <li>Takes consult in other men</li>
  <li>Does not get lost in tasks/duties and forgoes love, freedom, full consciousness.</li>
  <li>Always follows through on his word and remains in integrity with men and women</li>
  <li>Refrains from ejaculating in excess and can transmute ejaculation into non-ejaculatory orgasm</li>
  <li>Dissolves into the mystery and remerges full of love to give again and again without petering out!</li>
  <li>Maintains a full and open front of the body at all times</li>
  <li>Does not compromise his purpose for the relationship with his woman</li>
  <li>Does not instill “his way” onto his woman and instead instills the “best way” for her to grow in love and happiness.</li>
  <li>Entirely responsible for cutting through his own laziness, addictions, and unclarity.</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="masculine-relationship-is-required">Masculine relationship is required</h3>
<p>“If a man does not have a good relationship to masculine energy, then he will act like a woman and be hurt or defensive rather than make use of another man’s criticism.” Men’s teams are great for this.</p>

<h3 id="the-masculine-requires-a-purpose-to-live-fully">[[The masculine requires a purpose to live fully]]</h3>

<h3 id="on-women">On women</h3>
<p>[[what a feminine woman says is the sound of her feelings]]
[[A woman wants to relax knowing her man is in charge]]
[[A feminine woman responds to praise better than to challenge]]
[[Do not tolerate your woman’s moods of closure and complaint, instead open her up with skillful loving]]
[[At her core, a feminine woman is unpredictable, deep, potentially wild and destructive, serene, full of life, moved by the great force of her oceanic heart]]
[[Feel fully the energy from your attraction to her. Allow it to circulate in your body and use it to discover and give your gift]]</p>

<h3 id="the-masculine">The Masculine</h3>
<ul>
  <li>Always seeking a release from constraint into freedom</li>
  <li>Often does not understand feminine ways/needs
    <h3 id="the-feminine">The Feminine</h3>
  </li>
  <li>Always seeking love</li>
  <li>Often does not understand masculine ways/needs</li>
</ul>

<h3 id="unity">Unity</h3>
<p>[[the masculine seeks freedom, the feminine seeks love, and in the end both reach the same destination, the infinite ground of being which you are which is both absolute love and freedom]]</p>

<h3 id="on-attraction">On Attraction</h3>
<p>You NEED to maintain a polarized relationship with the feminine.</p>

<p>DO NOT DENY YOUR DESIRE TO THE FEMININE. YOU CANT JUST BE FRIENDS FOR INSTANCE. Sexual polarity is NECESSARY. YOU NEED TO ENSURE THIS.</p>

<p>Familiarity breeds de-polarization.</p>

<h1 id="highlights">Highlights</h1>
<h2 id="preface">Preface</h2>
<hr />
<p>The most valuable asset of a man in today’s world is his presence, his depth of awareness. You are not any of your identities or possessions. Know yourself as awareness. Embody yourself and let your actions come from this knowing.</p>

<p>“A man’s worth can be found in his depth of being. A shallow man, easily perturbed and swayed, is worth less to his woman and his world than a man whose presence is deeply sourced. A profound and steady gaze conveys truth more than furtive eyes. Full, even breathing is trusted more than shallow, jittery gasps. A man grounded in the unfathomable mystery of life, in touch with death’s vastness—rather than merely flitting from one busy surface activity to another—is sourced in his depth.” — location: <a href="kindle://book?action=open&amp;asin=B01NA993PI&amp;location=115">115</a> ^ref-38358</p>

<p>Identified with money or accomplishments, a man feels weak when he compares himself to others who have more. But when he knows himself to be self-radiant awareness, conscious and lit up, awakening as man, he blooms in perfect harmony with the immense energy of reality. The infinite force of now is his power and his presence. — location: <a href="kindle://book?action=open&amp;asin=B01NA993PI&amp;location=126">126</a> ^ref-11063</p>

<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<hr />
<p>Characteristics of the superior man:</p>
<ul>
  <li>purposeful</li>
  <li>confident</li>
  <li>directed</li>
  <li>integrity</li>
  <li>humorous</li>
  <li>sensitive</li>
  <li>spontaneous</li>
  <li>spiritually alive</li>
</ul>

<p>The superior man loves to take on his woman with so much love she vanishes. He is dedicated to creating love through his work and sexuality. He doesn’t hold on to his masculine nor feminine. He lives from his deepest core, committed to magnifying love.</p>

<p>[[Our culture pushes us to repress our sexuality]]</p>

<p>In the 1960’s society sought balance in 50/50 culture, men embraced the feminine and women embraced the masculine. A good thing. but this lead to confusion down the road, especially it lead to sexual neutrality.</p>

<p>[[Sexual attraction is based on sexual polarity between the masculine and the feminine]]</p>

<p>[[The loss of sexual passion stems from de-polarization between masculine and feminine]]</p>

<p>Love does not require this energetic polarity, just sex.</p>

<p>[[The masculine requires a purpose to live fully]]
[[The feminine are in search for love]]</p>

<p>Work obligations and family can kill your sexual attraction, along with spiritual depth and physical health.</p>

<p>Women in masculine roles have their femininity “dried up”</p>

<p>You need both heart and spine to be a superior man</p>

<h2 id="1-stop-hoping-for-a-completion-of-anything-in-life">1 Stop Hoping for a Completion of Anything in Life</h2>
<hr />
<p>There is no finalization to anything. No rest. Keep making love to this life and sharing your gift.</p>

<p>Just go and give your gift. Don’t wait.</p>

<p>Men who have lived significant lives are men who never waited: not for money, security, ease, or women. Feel what you want to give most as a gift, to your woman and to the world, and do what you can to give it today. Every moment waited is a moment wasted, and each wasted moment degrades your clarity of purpose. — location: <a href="kindle://book?action=open&amp;asin=B01NA993PI&amp;location=353">353</a> ^ref-39655</p>

<h2 id="2-live-with-an-open-heart-even-if-it-hurts">2 Live with an Open Heart Even if it Hurts</h2>
<hr />
<p>A superior man should be able to love from a place of pain. Stay in yourself always. Feel everything. Do not close down.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Reminds me of untethered soul by michael singer</p>
</blockquote>

<h2 id="4-know-your-real-edge-and-dont-fake-it">4 Know Your Real Edge and Don’t Fake It</h2>
<hr />
<p>“Your edge is where you stop short, or where you compromise your fullest gift, and, instead, cater to your fears.”</p>

<p>Live at the edge of discomfort. Don’t settle for mediocrity or comfort. That leads to feeling dead.</p>

<h2 id="5-always-hold-to-your-deepest-realization">5 Always Hold to your Deepest Realization</h2>
<hr />
<p>Live from the realization of who you are (source). Take action from infinite being. Steep yourself in a spiritual life (people and books). Keep grounded in source.</p>

<h2 id="6-never-change-your-mind-just-to-please-a-woman">6 Never Change Your Mind Just to Please a Woman</h2>
<hr />
<p>Don’t betray your deepest knowledge or intuition to please a woman or “go along” with her.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Stop agreeing with Esther</p>
</blockquote>

<p>If her decision is wise, go along with it. She needs to trust you, but YOU need to make the decision. You must act in accordance with your core. If you are wrong, you will grow and become wiser.</p>

<h2 id="7-your-purpose-must-come-before-your-relationship">7 Your Purpose Must Come Before Your Relationship</h2>
<hr />
<p>[[The masculine requires a purpose to live fully]]
If you need to spend time with your woman, give her ABSOLUTE ATTENTION</p>

<h2 id="8-lean-just-beyond-your-edge">8 Lean Just Beyond Your Edge</h2>
<hr />
<p>“Your fear is the sharpest definition of your self. You should know it. You should feel it virtually constantly. Fear needs to become your friend, so that you are no longer uncomfortable with it.” — location: <a href="kindle://book?action=open&amp;asin=B01NA993PI&amp;location=500">500</a> ^ref-11446</p>

<p>Own your fear and lean just beyond it, in every aspect of your life.</p>

<h2 id="9-do-it-for-love">9 Do It For Love</h2>
<hr />
<p>Do not penetrate your woman nor the world in a mediocre way. Use everything you’ve got to liberate your woman and the world into deep love/truth and openness.</p>

<p>[[Sex is a microcosm of the macrocosm of life]]</p>

<p>There are two paths:
1) Renounce the world/woman
2) Fuck both to smithereens. No gifts left ungiven. Lose and gain everything. No limit to depth of being. Die blissfully though a crucifixion of pain and pleasure.</p>
<h2 id="10-enjoy-your-friends-criticism">10 Enjoy Your Friend’s Criticism</h2>
<hr />
<p><strong>If a man does not have a good relationship to masculine energy, then he will act like a woman and be hurt or defensive rather than make use of another man’s criticism.</strong></p>

<p>Your men’s team should be willing to challenge your mediocrity by suggesting concrete actions. Offer brutal honesty.</p>

<p>“If you merely want support from your men friends without challenge, it bespeaks an unresolved issue you may have with your father, whether he is alive or dead.”</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Definitely can relate. I’ve been wanting support without challenge because of a lack of support from my own father</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Hang out with men who are living at their edge, facing their fears, and living just beyond them.</p>

<h2 id="11-if-you-dont-know-your-purpose-discover-it-now">11 If you don’t know your Purpose, Discover It, Now</h2>
<hr />
<blockquote>
  <p>I don’t know my purpose</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Without a life purpose, a man is lost. Adapting to events rather than creating events.</p>

<p>Your career must be aligned with your purpose</p>

<p>Recognize the truth. You are limitless consciousness. You are already full. The world or a partner cannot make you full. From this place you can give your gifts and vanish into this bliss of giving.</p>

<h2 id="12-be-willing-to-change-everything-in-your-life">12 Be Willing to Change Everything in Your Life</h2>
<hr />
<p>You must be capable of not knowing what to do in your life entering a period of unknowingness and waiting for a vision or a new form of purpose to emerge. You may need to work your way though lesser purposes to find your core purpose.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>In my case, lesser purpose might be having sex with multiple partners. My core purpose to commune with god</p>
</blockquote>

<table>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td>![blah](/assets/images/Drawing 2024-05-27 12.10.54.excalidraw</td>
      <td>center)</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<p>If the purpose you are following is feeling empty, boring, useless, then it should be discarded. This is a sign of growth. You then must cut into the next purpose.</p>

<p>Signs that you are completing a layer of purpose:</p>

<p>1) You suddenly have no interest whatsoever in a project or mission that, just previously, motivated you highly. 
2) ​You feel surprisingly free of any regrets whatsoever, for starting the project or for ending it
3) ​Even though you may not have the slightest idea of what you are going to do next, you feel clear, unconfused, and, especially, unburdened.
4) ​You feel an increase in energy at the prospect of ceasing your involvement with the project.
5) The project seems almost silly, like collecting shoelaces or wallpapering your house with gas station receipts. Sure, you could do it, but why would you want to?</p>

<p>It’s okay to wait for purpose to come.</p>

<p>Crazy things happen once you find your new purpose. Connections may be made. Love may be found. Wealth may be found.</p>

<h3 id="13-dont-use-your-family-as-an-excuse">13 Don’t Use Your Family as an Excuse</h3>
<hr />
<p>You may need to find your purpose before finding a woman. Purpose leads to presence which leads to a woman connecting with you.</p>

<p>[[The masculine requires a purpose to live fully]</p>

<p>For some men, their deepest life purpose is their family.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>I don’t find this to be true for me, at least now</p>
</blockquote>

<p>When being with children, be fully present for whatever time you have with them. Just like your woman.</p>

<p>Discover your deepest purpose and commit yourself completely to it, and find a way to embrace your family as you do so. But don’t let your family as an excuse to be less than you can be. This would be cheating your family of your fullest core.</p>

<h3 id="14-dont-get-lost-in-tasks-and-duties">14 Don’t Get Lost in Tasks and Duties</h3>
<hr />
<p>Tasks don’t get a man anywhere more conscious or free than he is capable of being in this present moment. — location: <a href="kindle://book?action=open&amp;asin=B01NA993PI&amp;location=737">737</a> ^ref-35850</p>

<p>The “do” mode is very common among men. Both strength (to plow through obstructions) and a weakness (not present, you just become a machine). You can’t find satisfaction in completing duties and tasks (do-ing). You must relax into the awe of the mystery of existence.</p>

<h3 id="15-stop-hoping-for-your-woman-to-get-easier">15 Stop Hoping for your Woman to Get Easier</h3>
<hr />
<p>A woman’s testing never ends. She wants you to be Shiva. She wants you to be a superior man.</p>

<p>You must be Shiva, the divine masculine: all-pervading, unperturbable. You woman is testing your Shiva-ness. She wants you to be this and to trust you and is testing if you get distracted or bend to her wiles.</p>

<p>Your success doesn’t mean anything unless you are free and loving. Nothing she says or does can collapse you.</p>

<p>Remain full and strong, humorous and happy.</p>

<p>[[A woman wants to relax knowing her man is in charge]]</p>

<p>The most loving women are the women who will test you the most.</p>

<h3 id="16-women-are-not-liars">16 Women Are Not Liars</h3>
<hr />
<p>The masculine means what it says. The feminine says what it feels.</p>

<p>[[what a feminine woman says is the sound of her feelings]]</p>

<h3 id="17-praise-her">17 Praise Her</h3>
<hr />
<p>The masculine grows by challenge. The feminine grows by praise.</p>

<p>[[A feminine woman responds to praise better than to challenge]]
 <strong>praise the tiny quality that you want to grow</strong></p>

<h3 id="18-tolerating-her-leads-to-resenting-her">18 Tolerating her Leads to Resenting Her</h3>
<hr />
<p>A man should not tolerate bitchy and complaining moodiness in his woman. He should server her with every ounce of skill and perseverance until she opens up into love.</p>

<p>Her difficult moments are opportunities to test your capacity to open her up. Humor and physically expressed love help open her up more than talking.</p>

<p>[[Do not tolerate your woman’s moods of closure and complaint, instead open her up with skillful loving]]</p>

<h3 id="19-dont-analyze-your-woman">19 Don’t Analyze Your Woman</h3>
<hr />
<p>Moods are more tidal in the feminine than the masculine. Do not analyze her. Almost all of a woman’s emotional problems stem from feeling unloved.</p>

<h3 id="20-dont-suggest-that-a-woman-fix-her-own-emotional-problem">20 Don’t Suggest That a Woman Fix Her Own Emotional Problem</h3>
<hr />
<p>The masculine is direct and to the point. Analyzing. A deep feminine desires is for the masculine to figure it out and guide her. [[A woman wants to relax knowing her man is in charge]].</p>

<p>You say to her, “Happy Birthday! For your birthday, we can do anything you want. We can go anywhere and do anything. And I’ll do anything for you. What do you want to do?” This is exactly the opposite of most women’s idea of an ideal birthday present. Most women would get far more excited if you were to say, “You’ve got thirty minutes to pack your bags. Don’t ask me where we’re going, but we’ll be gone for the weekend. Everything is taken care of. Just pack your bags, and leave the rest to me. I’m going to give you the best birthday you’ve ever had.” — location: <a href="kindle://book?action=open&amp;asin=B01NA993PI&amp;location=1000">1000</a> ^ref-6031</p>

<p>[[At her core, a feminine woman is unpredictable, deep, potentially wild and destructive, serene, full of life, moved by the great force of her oceanic heart]]</p>

<p>DO NOT ANALYZE HER BLOCKS</p>

<h3 id="21-stay-with-her-intensity-to-a-point">21 Stay with her Intensity to a Point</h3>
<hr />
<p>[[Do not tolerate your woman’s moods of closure and complaint, instead open her up with skillful loving]]</p>

<h3 id="22-dont-force-the-feminine-to-make-decisions">22 Don’t Force the Feminine to Make Decisions</h3>
<hr />
<p>If a man abnegates his responsibility to provide his gift of masculine clarity and decisiveness, she will become masculine herself, leading to depolarization. [[The loss of sexual passion stems from de-polarization between masculine and feminine]]</p>

<p>Always tell her what you would do and why, even if you think she should make her own decision.</p>

<h3 id="23-your-attraction-to-the-feminine-is-inevitable">23 Your Attraction to the Feminine is Inevitable</h3>
<hr />
<p>Feminine energy gets your out of your head and into your body. Attractiveness is equivalent to radiance in a woman. <strong>IT’S NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF</strong></p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Hear that, [[The Cocoon]]</p>
</blockquote>

<p>It is not DEMEANING for a woman to be the object of your polar attraction. You are negating your sexual essence by suppressing your natural desires.</p>

<p>It is not evil or bad to be attracted to women. This attraction is the same desire that leads to spiritual freedom.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>I KNOW THIS FROM MY PSYCHEDELIC EXPERIENCES</p>
</blockquote>

<p>“You don’t need to have sex with her to savor inexpressible joy”</p>

<p>Let the energy she provokes in you move through your body. This is a blessing.</p>
<h3 id="24-choose-a-woman-who-is-your-complementary-opposite">24 Choose a Woman who is your Complementary Opposite</h3>
<hr />
<p>[[Sexual attraction is based on sexual polarity between the masculine and the feminine]]</p>

<p>Choose a partner who is your sexual reciprocal</p>

<p>Very masculine is attracted to very feminine. Neutral is attracted to neutral. Highly polarized couples are more sexually passionate.</p>

<p>“The feminine body is free to be moved by love, and by life itself. And this is highly valued by most men; to behold a woman free in her expression of bodily ecstasy is one of the most awesome visions most men have had.” — location: <a href="kindle://book?action=open&amp;asin=B01NA993PI&amp;location=1210">1210</a> ^ref-41753</p>

<p>Women’s bodies are open to more sexual AND spiritual energy than men. A woman who is home in her feminine essence has no disconnection between sex and spirit. Her sexual surrender is the same as her spiritual surrender. She opens from head to toe.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>women who like to dance are more feminine</p>
</blockquote>

<p>The unique gift of the feminine form is to transform and inspire men by the power of their free feminine embodiment.</p>

<p>[[At her core, a feminine woman is unpredictable, deep, potentially wild and destructive, serene, full of life, moved by the great force of her oceanic heart]]</p>

<h3 id="25-know-what-is-important-in-your-woman">25 Know What is Important In Your Woman</h3>
<hr />
<p>If you aren’t clear about what’s important (friendship, sexual passion, parenting, business) each element will conflict with the other. attraction will diminish if you want everything from her blurred together.</p>

<p>Domesticity replaces mystery</p>

<p>Be careful. you must be skillful as to not diminish the potency of passion by squashing the fullness of her feminine energy into merely functional roles.</p>

<p>Know what is the purpose of your intimacy. align all other activities around this.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>For me, spiritual union through sexual intimacy is the purpose.</p>
</blockquote>

<h3 id="26-you-will-often-want-more-than-one-woman">26 You Will Often Want More Than One Woman</h3>
<hr />
<p>Any man who is masculine will desire sexual variety. There is no way to avoid it. It is not worth acting on such desires.</p>

<p>Your highest purpose is “to liberate yourself and others into love and freedom”. Therefore you should do whatever magnifies the love and freedom in your life and in the lives of those whom your actions affect.
<img src="/assets/images/20240702_145016.jpg" alt="blah" /></p>
<h5 id="on-multiple-partners">On multiple partners</h5>
<p>“How many women you have sex with is your business. Before you consider more than one, however, it is best to prove your capacity with one. If you can’t handle one—if deep communion, rejuvenating passion, and spiritual happiness are not the main features of your present intimacy—then you have not passed the test, and it is best to discipline your desire for other partners, since nobody is likely to be served.”</p>

<h3 id="27-young-women-offer-you-a-special-energy">27 Young Women Offer You A Special Energy</h3>
<hr />
<p>Young women usually don’t have masculine layers of functional protection built up over years of need. They are unobstructed feminine energy.</p>

<p>“Uncompromised, youthful, feminine energy turns you on and opens your heart. You actually feel happier around young women. You feel more energetic, alive, and loving. As women get older, they typically take on more and more masculine tasks and responsibilities in our culture, so their radiance begins to decrease”</p>

<p>It is your responsibility to honor the heart rejuvenative gift of a young woman without imposing your sexual desire upon her.</p>

<p>[[Mastering sexuality entails learning to sustain greater and greater degrees of pleasure and desire in the body without having to release it.]]</p>

<h3 id="28-each-woman-has-a-temperature-that-can-heal-or-irritate-you">28 Each Woman has a “Temperature” That Can Heal or Irritate You</h3>
<hr />
<p>Women have different energies, hot and cool. You need to know which one is best for you.</p>

<p>“When your life seems dreary and boring, a more spicy and hot woman will probably appeal to you. She will provide you with the fire you are missing. However, when your life is extremely challenging and you feel burnt out, a hot woman might be too much. You may be more attracted to the soothing gaze and touch of a cool woman.”</p>

<p>Needs may change throughout your life.</p>

<h3 id="29-choose-a-woman-who-chooses-you">29 Choose a Woman Who Chooses You</h3>
<hr />
<p>You need to be able to determine if a woman really wants him but is playing hard to get, or if she really doesn’t want him.</p>

<p>Ask your friends and even her friends for more information.</p>

<h3 id="30-what-she-wants-is-not-what-she-says">30 What She Wants is Not What She Says</h3>
<hr />
<p>Don’t be forced to do something against your will by her.</p>

<p>The divine masculine is consciousness. Ejaculation decreases consciousness. If your woman says she wants you unconscious, you must NOT give in.</p>

<p>Do not be swayed from your truth by her.</p>

<p>[[A woman wants to relax knowing her man is in charge]]</p>

<h3 id="31-her-complaint-is-content-free">31 Her Complaint is Content-Free</h3>
<hr />
<p>A woman always wants the divine masculine presence in a man. If this is not met, she will complain. <strong>Her complaints should ring like warning bells!</strong> Though the thing she is complaining about is rarely the thing she is complaining about. It’s not the content. <strong>She is complaining that you are not conscious, happy, fearless, humorous, loving, giving your fullest gift to the world</strong>.</p>

<p>Your lack of integrity will cause her to build up her own masculine protection mechanism. This will de-polarize your relationship.</p>

<h3 id="32-she-doesnt-really-want-to-be-number-one">32 She Doesn’t Really Want to be Number One</h3>
<hr />
<p>A man’s higher purpose is his priority, not his intimacy.</p>

<p>Your purpose comes before your relationship. If this is not the case for you, she will feel smothered by neediness and clinging.</p>

<h3 id="33-your-excellent-track-record-is-meaningless-to-her">33 Your Excellent Track Record is Meaningless to Her</h3>
<hr />
<p>Men base other men on their track record. A few slip ups here and there don’t matter. Women base men on how she’s feeling in the moment, forgetting past behavior. To a woman, what counts is the feeling in the moment, not the history.</p>

<p>If you find her shut down because of something your did, [[Do not tolerate your woman’s moods of closure and complaint, instead open her up with skillful loving]]</p>

<h3 id="34-she-wants-to-relax-in-the-demonstration-of-your-direction">34 She wants to Relax in the Demonstration of your Direction</h3>
<hr />
<p>[[A woman wants to relax knowing her man is in charge]]</p>

<p>You (masculine) need to take charge for your woman to be in the feminine. It means you need to know where you are heading and how you are going to get there in every way.</p>

<p>Do not be ambiguous. Have a plan. Be organized.</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>My excursion into GTD and obsidian are making this come back for me</p>
</blockquote>

<p>It doesn’t matter if she earns more or less than you, as long as she can feel your loving wisdom and clarity in direction.</p>

<h3 id="35-you-are-always-searching-for-freedom">35 You are Always Searching for Freedom</h3>
<hr />
<p>The masculine is always seeking release from constraint into freedom (orgasm, freedom from death). All masculine goals are directed toward more freedom. This is why men like war and sports (we have to get free, to the other side).</p>

<p><strong>[[Release yourself enough to relax into the depth of absolute freedom]]</strong> Relax into the depths of yourself. Your freedom. It is the end of the masculine “game”. By playing the game you only “taste” this freedom.</p>

<p>The “ah” of insight in philosophy is a release into freedom!</p>

<p>Women seek love not freedom. Not emptiness but fullness. her means is not release but surrender.</p>

<p>“Her dark side enjoys the emotional aggression in soap operas and romance novels, rather than the physical aggression of boxing matches and porno movies.”</p>

<p>[[the masculine seeks freedom, the feminine seeks love, and in the end both reach the same destination, the infinite ground of being which you are which is both absolute love and freedom]]</p>

<p>Combining masculine and feminine you add freedom to love.</p>

<p>“In the end, the feminine search for love and the masculine search for freedom reach the same destination: the unbounded and infinite ground of being who you are, which is both absolute love and freedom.”</p>

<h3 id="36-own-your-darkest-desires">36 Own your Darkest Desires</h3>
<hr />
<p>“If a man disowns his dark masculine desire for freedom, then he kinks the hose of his masculine force. His energy will not flow freely, and his attention will be bound by unfulfilled yearnings. Most importantly, if his hose is kinked in this way, he weakens his masculine capacity to stand fearless in the death that is conscious life. He will not be able to face the unknown, the groundless ground of being, and still function from his heart in love.”</p>

<p>The desire to ravish a woman is the same masculine desire to break through opponents, break through philosophical barriers to intellectual insight, break through the fear of death into spiritual freedom.</p>

<p>When the desire to ravish becomes disconnected from your heart, then you will settle for breaking through a woman’s resistances without love through violence or coercion.</p>

<p>The dark feminine desire to be raped is as strong as the dark masculine desire to rape.</p>

<p><strong>Ravishment is rape plus love.</strong></p>

<p>You have to be willing to play these dark poles in love and humor otherwise they will appear in loveless ways.</p>

<p><strong>You must be as fearless with your sexual desire as you are with your spiritual desire</strong>, Don’t be afraid to lose yourself with your woman into the unknowable infinity beyond the mind. Most men are.<img src="/assets/images/20240716_133223.jpg" alt="blah" /></p>

<p>When you make love, feel through your own boundaries into her. feel her so deeply you are aware of her breath, movements, her emotions.</p>

<p>Allow love to ravish your woman to bursting, filling her beyond capacity. let go of all fear, giving only love.</p>

<p>Allow both dark and light desires.</p>

<p>By reclaiming the full force of masculine loving, you will re-own your capacity to ravish your woman and you will re-own your spiritual guts.</p>

<p>“To truly ravish your woman in love, you must yield yourself in the worship and trust of her heart, which, in truth, is your heart. Such fearlessness will prepare you for and perhaps even initiate you into the worship and trust of consciousness itself, such that you will find greater and greater capacity to yield into and as the boundless One who you truly are.”</p>

<h3 id="37-she-wants-the-killer-in-you">37 She wants the “Killer” in You</h3>
<hr />
<p>Fearlessness is a quintessential form of the ultimate masculine gift. Fearlessness is the capacity to transcend the fear of death for the sake of love.</p>

<p>Today’s society creates wimpy men.</p>

<p>“But beneath the nice veneer of most women lies the wrathful goddess who would chop the head off of every mediocre “new age” man. And beneath the patient smile of most men lies the warrior of love who would ravish his woman into bliss rather than listen to her chat in pointless emotional circles”</p>

<p><strong>The dark masculine energy has been suppressed nowadays</strong></p>

<p>Your woman wants to feel your capacity to stand strong in your own desires and ravish her because you love her, unafraid of her dark energy. She wants to know your capacity to <strong>face and know death</strong>. The knowledge of death strips the armor from your heart and allows the knowledge of love..</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>This is why I should get back into flying. OWN it.</p>
</blockquote>

<p>“The “killer” your woman wants is the one who knows that life is a process of dying through to that which cannot be lost. Only in this sacrifice of fear can your heart remain unguarded. Facing the potential burglar at night is only a sign to your woman that you are willing to lose everything into love.”</p>

<h3 id="38-she-needs-your-consciousness-to-match-her-energy">38 She Needs Your Consciousness to Match Her Energy</h3>
<hr />
<p>She will test you first on your dark side. Only after this trust is established will trusting proceed towards the light.</p>

<p>She will continually test your weak spots. She will return to the energies that you cannot match, constantly testing your capacities.</p>

<p><strong>She wants your consciousness (clear strong and free) as much as you want he radiance.</strong> If you are not penetrating her moods, she can’t feel your consciousness.</p>

<p><strong>You must communicate your consciousness through your body. Your fearlessness and strength of love must manifest though your body.</strong> “If you walk up to her, hold her in your arms, and laugh affectionately in the humor of the moment, she will feel your freedom, if it is for real. She will feel it because it is communicated through your body.”</p>

<p>==<strong>“Your body, tone of voice, and the look in your eyes mean a lot more to her than anything you could say.”</strong>==</p>

<p>Wo<img src="/assets/images/20240807_221601.jpg" alt="blah" />rds come later.</p>

<p>“She will never trust your “lighter” masculine capacities until you have proven your “darker” masculine capacities.”</p>

<p>If she is a good woman, she will test you with her darkest moods over and over until your consciousness is unperturbed by feminine challenge, and you are able to pervade her with your love, just like you are here to pervade the world. In response, she will drench your world in love and light.</p>

<h3 id="39-the-feminine-is-abundant">39 The Feminine is Abundant</h3>
<hr />
<p><strong>There is never a shortage of women or feminine energy. “There are no good women” is never true</strong></p>

<p>You are living in an ocean of feminine energy right now (nature). If you feel stranded on your own masculine island of weariness and hunger, its because you are refusing to embrace the energy and women around you.</p>

<p>Feel the women around you as walking blessings of energy. Receive their sexiness, happiness as restorative blissfulness.</p>

<h3 id="40-allow-older-women-their-magic">40 Allow Older Women Their Magic</h3>
<hr />
<p>Feminine radiance is not only the appearance of a woman, but the shine of life force itself. <strong>If you are disconnected to your deep masculine core of purpose and consciousness, you will also be disconnected from a woman’s depth. You will only be attracted to the superficial display of a woman’s radiance</strong>.</p>

<p>“The natural sexiness of a young woman will always give you energy. You never need to deny this. But the awesome beauty and radiant ease of a deep woman can stop your mind, widen your heart, and suspend your body in the mystery of feminine grace, all in an instant, with a single gaze or touch, regardless of her body’s age. And in relationship with such a woman, there are no bounds to the rapture which may resonate through your union. Boundless feminine love-radiance and temporary physical sexiness are both blessings; you must decide, moment by moment, and year by year, which qualities you will invoke and venerate with your attention, praise, and union.”</p>

<h3 id="41-turn-your-list-into-gifts">41 Turn Your List Into Gifts</h3>
<hr />
<p>A man should learn to circulate this heightened energy in his body rather than dispersing it.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>How do I do this? Does the author have another book that details this?</p>
</blockquote>

<p>It’s women that makes a man interested in the world.</p>

<p><strong>You can wean yourself from the addictive cycles of sexuality and intoxication by transforming your lust</strong></p>

<p><strong>Use your breath to circulate the energy. Inhale it into your heart. On the exhale, move into the world and penetrate it.</strong></p>

<p>Allow women’s sexiness to motivate and inspire you rather than beguile you to masturbate.</p>

<p>[[Feel fully the energy from your attraction to her. Allow it to circulate in your body and use it to discover and give your gift]]</p>

<h3 id="42-never-allow-your-desire-to-become-suppressed-or-depolarized">42 Never Allow Your Desire To Become Suppressed Or Depolarized</h3>
<hr />
<p>DO NOT DENY YOUR DESIRE TO THE FEMININE. YOU CANT JUST BE FRIENDS. Sexual polarity is NECESSARY. YOU NEED TO ENSURE THIS</p>

<p>Familiarity breeds depolarization and depolarization breeds contempt amongst lovers. With depolarization you become sexually neutral and may prefer other women more easily.</p>

<p>Women likely feel the sexual depolarization before you do.</p>

<p>De-polarization is the man’s fault. You have control over the passion and desire in the relationship. Nurture this.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>Justin Sterling says this ^^</p>
</blockquote>

<h3 id="43-use-her-attractiveness-as-a-slingshot-through-appearance">43 Use Her Attractiveness As A Slingshot Through Appearance</h3>
<hr />
<p>Use her attractiveness as a slingshot through her appearance into source.</p>

<p>Women cannot satisfy you absolutely. NOTHING CAN :)</p>

<p>“The play of your body wanting her body is the most obvious hoax of fulfillment”</p>

<p>Women are the epitome of appearance, and all appearances seem to promise you something you want. But it is the source behind the appearance you are looking for.</p>

<p>“You are least unhappy when you are relieved of the need to get anything at all from appearance.”</p>

<p>“You are chasing your own tail, and much of the time that tail looks suspiciously like a woman”</p>

<p><strong>But do NOT stop chasing</strong></p>

<p>“Your ultimate desire is for the union of consciousness with its own luminosity, wherein all appearance is recognized as your deep, blissful nature, and there is only One. Your desire for union with a woman is a stepped-down version of this ultimate spiritual need. You can use your desire as a doorway to spiritual oneness. Magnify your desiring to the brink of madness. Sustain it with full breath, relaxed body, and open heart. Embrace your woman, if you have one, and give her what you want from her. Give it all to her. Give it away to her. Give her so much of what you want from her that you can’t tell who is who, the chaser has become the tail, and all motion stops in the intensity of self-release. There is only One. The very light of your consciousness shines as the world, and it is looking back at you, appearing as woman. She often appears as what you most fear and desire. She is the goddess, ready to fuck you, murder you, and enlighten you. Her appearance and your desire can be an endless drama of need, or they can merge, becoming a doorway to your divine source.”</p>

<p><strong>Other is a mirage. feel through other to get to oneness,</strong></p>

<p>“The revelation of deep oneness is love.”</p>

<p>Appearances are distractions (tits, ass, wealth, fame). Bow down through them into the deep which only seems to have been an other. For there is only the one.</p>

<h3 id="44-ejaculation-should-be-converted-or-consciously-chosen">44 Ejaculation Should Be Converted Or Consciously Chosen</h3>
<hr />
<p>Many reasons for converting ejaculation into non-ejaculatory whole body, brain, heart orgasms.</p>
<ul>
  <li>Physical</li>
  <li>Spiritual</li>
  <li>Relational</li>
</ul>

<p>On relational:
The woman knows she can deplete him, empty him of life force. She feels he cannot be trusted because both she and the world can deplete and depolarize him.</p>

<p>[[Dont ejaculate to preserve the polarity in your relationship. Because she cannot put out your fire]]</p>

<p>Wit<img src="/assets/images/20240820_144524.jpg" alt="blah" />hout ejaculating, you build up energy to “cut through” the obstructions of life to give your gift.
“In a subtle way, excess ejaculations will diminish your courage to take risks, professionally and spiritually.”</p>

<p>What ravishes your woman is invading her body with your consciousness. Not your semen.</p>

<p>if your woman knows you can allow temporary pleasures to diminish your capacity for her, she knows you will succumb to the world as well.</p>

<p>You are to endlessly ravish her and the world.</p>

<p>Avoid women who refuse your loving.</p>

<p>“Your masculine sexual gift is to coax, humor, shock, and caress her love into melting through her layers of fear. Without imposing your own needs on her, let your love penetrate to the deep part of her that is totally open to love, that is love itself, and coax it to the fore. Do this slowly, over time, not through conversation, but through bodily communicated presence, care, consciousness, and the liquid loving of sexual intermingling. When she feels the absolutely trustable nature of your loving—that you are truly with her, committed to loving, and you’re not going to get lost in the self-enclosed spasm of your own pleasurizing—she will begin to trust you with her most vulnerable core.”</p>

<p>“Every time she sucks you into an uncontrollable need to ejaculate, she has conquered you. She controls you and masters you. She is in charge, sexually, no matter what manly gestures you make before ejaculating. With a simple flick of her tongue, a silky moan, or a slurping tilt of her pelvis, she can drain you of life. And, deep down, she knows the world can do the same to you.”</p>

<p>Do not surrender for less than the total surrender of her heart and your own into the fullness of divine union. The pleasures of this far exceed the typical genital pleasures.</p>

<p>if you are addicted to ejaculation, your woman will be sexually emotionally and spiritually unfulfilled.</p>

<p>A superior man dissolves into the mystery and remergest full of love to give again and again without petering out!</p>

<h3 id="45-breathe-down-the-front">45 Breathe Down The Front</h3>
<hr />
<p>Most men have blocks down the front of their body. A key to mastering woman and world is maintaining a full and open front of the body at all times.</p>

<p>Your belly is where your energy meets the world</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Lower dantian?</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Relaxed, poised, attentive with an open front. <strong>Not wrapped up in self concern.</strong></p>

<p>Your breath needs to reach the belly to recharge your batteries. otherwise you will feel weak and unsure of yourself. Your breath is your primary extension of your personal energy. You can also use your breath to open other people’s knots of tension.</p>

<p>When engaging with others, inhale into the front of your body, open all the knots, feel the stress dissolve in the ocean of love on your exhale. Feeling the unease of others, opening up their unease.</p>

<p>And breathe like this during sex.</p>

<h3 id="46-ejaculate-up-the-spine">46 Ejaculate Up The Spine</h3>
<hr />
<p>Convert depletive ejaculatory orgasms into rejuvenative orgasms, through contracting the pelvic floor and drawing energy up the spine.</p>

<p>Best definition of premature ejaculation: “If your ejaculation signs the end to your session of loving before both you and your woman have fully opened yourselves, then your ejaculation is premature”</p>

<p>We are conditioned as teenagers that ejaculation is the goal, to release tension.</p>

<p>To realize the full potential of sex, you need to learn how to recondition your body and nervous system to unhabitualize the mechanics of ejaculation and convert orgasm into massive energy.</p>

<p>Step 1: Relax muscles instead of tensing up
Step 2: Redirect your attention to feel your partner rather than your own sensations</p>

<p>With practice you will be able to [[feel through your partner during sex]]</p>

<p>A large part of avoiding PE is to breathe fully, deeply, and with great force throughout the day</p>
<blockquote>
  <p>Breathwork?</p>
</blockquote>

<p>Inhale down the front of your body, filling belly and genitals. Exhale up your spine.</p>

<p>Sex increases the life force in your body, tending to be more focused in the genitals. you need to be careful to not let it build up and therefore move the energy.</p>

<p>You need to practice both contracting your pelvic floor AND also pulling the entire floor upwards towards your body.</p>

<p>#==”While you are having sex, but before you are close to ejaculating, practice contracting your pelvic floor as just discussed. While you contract it and pull upward, breathe the energy up your spine. You will have to experiment to determine whether to inhale or to exhale the energy up your spine, although most people find that exhaling up the spine works best. If you combine the upward contraction of your pelvic floor with breathing up your spine, you should lose just a little bit of your erection as well as the need to ejaculate. As you continue making love, repeat this exercise as often as you need to in order to maintain relaxation and openness. Even while practicing this technique, you may notice that you occasionally come very close to having an orgasm. At this point, stop moving, apply the upward contraction of your pelvic floor, and breathe the orgasm energy up your spine. In addition to the upward contraction of your pelvic floor while breathing up the spine, some men find it helpful to clench their fists and teeth while looking upward with their eyes, especially when the urge toward ejaculation is particularly strong. With practice, however, all the muscular action becomes very subtle and gentle, until the entire exercise is done primarily through your breath, feeling, and intention. When the energy shoots up your spine, relax and enjoy the colors, feelings, and blisses that will fill your head and rain down through your body. Once you are proficient at this exercise, you can evoke the same sensations in your partner by feeling into your partner from your heart as the orgasm shoots up your spine. The upward movement of your energy will magnetize the same movement in hers. These practices will not be successful unless you are able to surrender as love in the midst of sexual embrace. Love is the governor of energy. More and more, you must practice being love in the form of sexual coupling. Regardless of how tough your day has been, regardless of the burdens you face in your life, sexing should be a time of practicing love. Like meditation or prayer, sex should be a special time of practicing opening your heart and giving love fully, into and through your partner, and in communion with that which you hold most sacred. If your heart is closed, your energy will be obstructed, and you will never be able to convert your spurt to a lightning bolt of love. If you don’t practice love, your sexual energy will be governed by old habits of body and emotion, which are all about the tiny commotion of ejaculation. So, if you want to expand sexual bliss as fully as possible, remember that your emotional disposition is far more important than the technical exercises themselves.”==</p>

<p><strong>These practices require you to be able to surrender as love within a sexual embrace.</strong></p>

<p>This requires experimentation and practice, but it is SOO worth it.</p>

<p>1) ​Rather than fantasizing or entertaining inward sexual imagery of any kind, remain totally present, aware of your own body, breath, and mind, and especially attentive to your partner. Break the masturbatory habit of inward fantasy by consciously practicing sex as a relational play of love with your partner. 
2) ​Keep your body and breath relaxed and full. Especially keep the front of your body relaxed, so that your belly is vast and your heart is soft and wide. This will help prevent too much tension from accumulating in any one area.
3) ​Learn to feel into, and then through, your partner, so that your attention is directed beyond your own sensations and even beyond your partner’s sensations. Practice feeling outward, without limit, as if you were feeling to infinity. In other words, whatever you are feeling, feel it fully, and then feel through and beyond it, so that sex becomes a constant feeling through and beyond every sensation, rather than focusing on any particular sensation. 
4) Throughout the day and during the sexual session, practice breathing so that your inhalation moves energy down the front of your body and the exhalation moves energy up your spine. Excessive, chronic thinking or addiction to ejaculation is often a sign that your energy is blocked and you are not yet breathing fully in this circle throughout the day.
5) During sex, occasionally practice the upward contraction of the floor of your pelvis while breathing sexual energy up your spine, so it fills your whole body. Especially as you begin to approach orgasm, you can combine the upward contraction of your pelvic floor with breathing up the spine in order to shoot your orgasm up into your brain, and even out through the top of your head, rather than down and out your genitals. This upward orgasm will then feel like it is gently seeping down through every cell of your body, saturating you with thick open light.”</p>

<h3 id="47-take-into-account-the-primary-asymmetry">47 Take Into Account the Primary Asymmetry</h3>
<hr />

<p>[[the masculine seeks freedom, the feminine seeks love, and in the end both reach the same destination, the infinite ground of being which you are which is both absolute love and freedom]]</p>

<p>To the masculine, purpose is primary. Intimacy is enjoyed only in addition to your purpose. To a woman, intimacy is at the core of her life. This is the primacy asymmetry.</p>

<p>A man’s priority is his mission, so he will gravitate to a woman who he feels would support his mission.</p>

<p>A man has many options for intimacy. A woman has only one.</p>

<p>It will never work for a woman to absorb herself in her career. This only works for men, whose mission is primary.</p>

<p>Feminism promotes anti-feminitity: “Our culture has become so anti-feminine that many women are trying to deny their feminine core desires and adopt the masculine way of dedication to mission. By denying their feminine essence, such women are predisposing themselves to emptiness of heart, depression, and bodily symptoms of disease”</p>

<p>Do not fake being concerned about the relationship as much as your woman. Be authentic to your core desires and dedicate your life with impeccability to your highest goals.</p>

<p>You become more present, more loving, more humorous when your life is truly aligned with your highest purpose.</p>

<h3 id="48-you-are-responsible-for-the-growth-in-intimacy">48 You Are Responsible For the Growth In Intimacy</h3>
<hr />
<p>“The man is responsible for the woman’s depth of love, or openness of mood, and the woman is responsible for the man’s “erection” or energy in the body”</p>

<p>It is hard for women to get out of her moods. But the masculine can do this, not as her therapist but as her wake-up call, her heart-opener. You need to know what she is missing that makes her feel unfulfilled (exercise, dance, time with friends). Your main gift is to guide her moment by moment out of her moods and into the openness of loving.</p>

<p>A woman can get you out of your head and into your body through her touch, loving, attractiveness. Bring you into presense.</p>

<h3 id="49-insist-on-practice-and-growth">49 Insist On Practice and Growth</h3>
<hr />
<p>Rather than wanting “his way”, a superior man wants the “growth way” for his woman, directing her into more love and happiness.</p>

<p>Men get too focused on the grind. Women get too focused on their moods. You must cut-through the grind to remember your purpose and you must cut-through her moods to her love.</p>

<p>==”You are entirely responsible for cutting through your own laziness, addictions, and unclarity”==</p>

<p>“You could meditate until you’re blue in the face, but it won’t work, if, when it comes down to it, you’d rather masturbate, read the newspaper, or watch TV than cut through your addictions, discipline your daily life, and give your gift from your deepest, most blissful source. The quality of your intent and the consistency and depth of your application determine the results of your direction in gifting—as well as your capacity to guide your woman’s life into greater happiness and bodily surrender into love.”</p>

<h3 id="50-restore-your-purpose-in-solitude-and-with-other-men">50 Restore Your Purpose In Solitude And With Other Men</h3>
<hr />
<p>“A man rediscovers and fine tunes his purpose in solitude, in challenging situations, and in the company of other men who won’t settle for his bullshit. But women strengthen their feminine radiance best in the company of other women in mutual celebration and play. A man must arrange for both forms of restoration: his own solitude and men’s gatherings, and his woman’s time with other women.”</p>

<p>If woman and man spend too much time with each other, they become neutralized.</p>

<p>Singing and dancing in the woods to reclaim your feminine. Remain in isolation and challenge yourself and live in austerity to reclaim your masculine.</p>

<p>“Unadorned suffering is the bedmate of masculine growth”</p>

<p>“Feel your suffering, rest with it, embrace it, make love with it. Feel your suffering so deeply and thoroughly that you penetrate it, and realize its fearful foundation. Almost everything you do, you do because you are afraid to die. And yet dying is exactly what you are doing, from the moment you are born. Two hours of absorption in a good Super Bowl telecast may distract you temporarily, but the fact remains. You were born as a sacrifice. And you can either participate in the sacrifice, dissolving in the giving of your gift, or you can resist it, which is your suffering.”</p>

<p>“Make sure that you arrange for your woman’s rejuvenative time and your own. Otherwise, you will rot in the cushions of bargained stagnation and sexual neutralization which pad your true edge of living your gift in relationship.”</p>

<h3 id="51-practice-dissolving">51 Practice Dissolving</h3>
<hr />
<p>Die in the giving of your gift</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="asshat" /><category term="blogpost" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Header of the page Welcome to my page assholes.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">SecondPost</title><link href="/2025/01/26/SecondPost.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="SecondPost" /><published>2025-01-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2025/01/26/SecondPost</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/26/SecondPost.html"><![CDATA[<p>Yeah baby</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/gtd.png" alt="blah" /></p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blogpost" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah baby]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">One More</title><link href="/1989/02/02/One-more.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="One More" /><published>1989-02-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>1989-02-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/1989/02/02/One-more</id><content type="html" xml:base="/1989/02/02/One-more.html"><![CDATA[<p>one more for the win</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blogpost" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[one more for the win]]></summary></entry></feed>