<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.10.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-01-31T23:12:41-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Matt Krolick</title><subtitle>A digital presence.</subtitle><author><name>Matt Krolick</name></author><entry><title type="html">Who are you?</title><link href="/2025/01/26/BlogPost-First.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Who are you?" /><published>2025-01-26T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-01-26T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2025/01/26/BlogPost---First</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2025/01/26/BlogPost-First.html"><![CDATA[<blockquote>
  <p>“The sense of being perched somewhere behind your eyes, looking out at a world that is separate from yourself—can be altered or entirely extinguished. Although such experiences of ‘self-transcendence’ are generally thought about in religious terms, there is nothing, in principle, irrational about them. From both a scientific and a philosophical point of view, they represent a clearer understanding of the way things are. Deepening that understanding, and repeatedly cutting through the illusion of the self, is what is meant by ‘spirituality’ in the context of this book.”          -<a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00LWM6CAM/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?_encoding=UTF8&amp;btkr=1">Waking Up: Searching for Spirituality Without Religion</a></p>
</blockquote>

<p>I read these words from Sam Harris’ book in 2017 though I had no understanding what he meant, until 7 years later. I had spent nearly a decade dabbling around with meditation, trying to extract the clinical benefits: lower stress, better sleep, reducing my suffering. I couldn’t develop a stable routine. Glimpses of relief here and there but ultimately frustration would get the better of me.</p>

<p>I am now in the Mayan jungle in Quintana Roo, MX, not to far from the border of Belize. I am lying on a mattress in the middle of circular thatch roof structure, a Maloka. A skylight is centered directly above me. I can see birds in the rafters. I’ve been here for nearly a week for several ayahuasca ceremonies. I am hardly eating and am ripped open emotionally, it feels like I am bleeding. I am exhausted and terrified of what’s about to happen.</p>

<p>I was told that this would be a quick journey. Two points of advice were given to me: “You are going to feel like you are dying. Just accept death. And.. don’t forget to breathe”. Dark red powder in some fancy glassware sealed with aluminum foil was presented to me along with a metal straw. When given the signal, I was to pierce the foil with the straw and breathe the smoke of the powder being vaporized.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/DALL·E 2025-01-31 22.50.05 - Aerial view from 50 feet above the ground of a traditional maloka, a round thatched-roof structure with a central glass skylight. The maloka is surrou.webp" alt="blah" /></p>]]></content><author><name>Matt Krolick</name></author><category term="blogpost" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The sense of being perched somewhere behind your eyes, looking out at a world that is separate from yourself—can be altered or entirely extinguished. Although such experiences of ‘self-transcendence’ are generally thought about in religious terms, there is nothing, in principle, irrational about them. From both a scientific and a philosophical point of view, they represent a clearer understanding of the way things are. Deepening that understanding, and repeatedly cutting through the illusion of the self, is what is meant by ‘spirituality’ in the context of this book.” -Waking Up: Searching for Spirituality Without Religion]]></summary></entry></feed>